best-price.com 2007-06-29

# Price Comparison and Test on www.Best-Price.com

|  Your Privacy   
---  
Best-price.com (the "Sites") are brought to you by Best-Price.com Ltd. ("Best-price.com"). Best-price.com believes that trust is an important component of the service we provide to our customers. To ensure that we earn and keep that trust, Best-price.com makes every effort to protect your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. This Privacy Policy is provided to inform you about Best-price.com's collection, use and disclosure of information you choose to share with us through the Sites.

This Privacy Policy is considered to be a part of Best-price.com's User Agreement. By using the Sites you agree to the terms and conditions of the User Agreement, including this Privacy Policy. By using the Sites, you are also consenting to Best-price.com's privacy practices, including the use and disclosure of any personally identifiable information that you have shared with us, as described in this Privacy Policy.   
  
Minor's Privacy   
The Sites are not targeted towards, or intended for use by anyone under the age of 18. By using the Sites you represent and warrant that you are 18 years of age or older. We reserve the right to terminate your membership in the event that Best-price.com becomes aware you are under 18. Persons under 18 may not submit any personally identifiable information to us, and if we discover that we have inadvertently gathered such information, we will take the appropriate steps to delete it.   
What Information We Collect   
**Information You Give Us.** The use of certain features and services on the Sites requires that you register and supply personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, telephone number and other information, which is stored by Best-price.com. When you register as a member of the Sites, we may also collect additional information from you in order to provide you with those specific services and to personalize your experience on the Sites. For example, Best-Price.com users may provide more information using features such as Wish Lists, and that information will be stored with your user profile.

**Information Gathered Automatically.** The Sites use "cookies" to automatically recognize returning users. Cookies used by the Sites may contain your user name, email address, IP address or zip code. A cookie is a small file on your hard drive that allows us to display your previously defined search criteria and notification preferences whenever you visit our site. "Clear gifs" are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and may be used to track the online movements of Web users or to let us know if you have opened an email that we sent you.

Your access provider assigns an internet protocol address to your computer when you use the Internet. We collect each IP address that accesses the Sites; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; your behavior on the Sites and related services, including the products and merchants you view or searched for, as well as the URL you come from and go to next; cookie number; participating merchants you visit and the items that you purchase. We use this data, as well as other data in our databases, to analyze site and user behavior, troubleshoot technical problems, resolve disputes, address complaints, prepare aggregated reports that we share with others and customize your experience on the Sites.

You can block cookies by changing the settings on your browser (contact your ISP for help), but doing so may prevent us from delivering certain services to you (e.g., saved searches). Your browser must also be set to accept cookies in order to access the Sites as a registered member.

**Other Data Collection.** We may get data from or about you in other ways not specifically described in this statement. For example, you might contact Community Care or customer support, or we may get a third party complaint about you.   
  
Use of Information by Best-price.com   
Information you provide to us through the Sites is used by Best-price.com to operate the Sites, provide you with information and services you request, and to communicate with you. We may, for example, use information you provide to target ads that we think you may be interested in, or send emails to you including newsletters and alerts. Your information may also be used to contact you when necessary (such as to assist you in your use of the Sites). You may always choose not to provide us with this information; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time (see the Choice/Opt-Out section below); however, you may not opt-out of some administrative emails (such as emails about User Agreement changes or communications about rebates earned in the Best-price.com Cash Back Program) while you are a member with one or more of our Sites.   
Sharing and Disclosure of Information   
**Aggregated Research Data.** Best-price.com produces research reports and other information and data about online shopping for participating merchants, and other customers, as well as media and other interested parties. Such information and data are based on aggregated, anonymous information about millions on online shoppers and do not include any personally identifiable information about individuals.

**Co-Branded Services.** Best-price.com usually saves information that it collects from users and shares this information with certain partners in order to provide services to users. In order to use certain services on the Sites, it may be necessary for you to enter information that then goes to our partner. The areas of the Sites in which partners are collecting information may be co-branded with our partners' logos. In these cases, the partner's use of user data is governed by their privacy policies, not ours. Best-price.com may receive a copy of such information from these partners, subject to the privacy policies of such partners. If you have questions regarding the privacy policy or data collection practices of one of our business partners, please contact that partner directly. Best-price.com does not have control over and is not responsible for the data collection and use practices of our business partners.

**Partners.** When you register as a member of the Sites, we will automatically enroll you in the Best-price.com Smart Shopper Club. Administration of this program may require that we share some of your personal data with one or more of our partners.

**Advertisers.** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Sites. These companies may use information about your visits to the Sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. When we do this, we do not provide your name, address, email address or telephone number.

Third party ad servers (including Falk) may place or recognize a cookie and, using the cookie or otherwise, collect and use data from your visits to the Sites and other websites to serve ads to you. For more about Falk's practices and your options regarding their data collection and use, see Falk's Privacy Policy.

**Other.** We may share your information with our affiliates, consultants, vendors and service providers, who assist us in maintaining the Sites and providing related services such as online registration for events. For example, we currently use a third party service provider to send rebate checks earned by participation in the Best-price.com Cash Back Program. In addition, Category Leads may have access to some or all of our Best-Price.com databases.

**Other Disclosures.** In addition, we may share data with any parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, and other companies under a common control or acquirers. As our business evolves, Best-price.com may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, reorganization, or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy. In such an event, personal and anonymous information may be one of the assets transferred.

We may disclose information when required by law or under the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to conform to applicable law, comply with legal process served on Best-price.com, or to protect the property or interests of Best-price.com, its agents and employees, personal safety, or the public. Under such circumstances, Best-price.com may be prohibited by law, court order or other legal process from providing notice of the disclosure, and Best-price.com reserves the right not to provide such notice in its sole discretion.   
  
Other Use and Disclosure of Information for the Sites   
**Content and Ratings.** You can publish reviews, comments and other content. Members can choose to rate products or reviews, and to create a web of trust. As an unregistered visitor, we may allow you to rate products and/or reviews.

Your review ratings and trust statements are displayed publicly unless you change the default configuration. Your member name is automatically displayed with reviews and comments you publish, and if other members choose to, they can receive email notifications of your publications or publish their own comments to your reviews.

We, and our licensees, can republish your content as described in our User Agreement. We publish product ratings and use them to develop aggregate ratings, personalize site views and merchandise products. We use your review ratings and web of trust to personalize site views and identify/feature popular members. For example, we may promote most popular or highest-earning reviews and members. While we don't expect to transfer the complete review rating and web of trust database to others (except as contemplated elsewhere in this Policy), we use the database throughout our network and to generate results for others.

**Email Tools.** If you send emails through our site, your email will include your email address and any personal message you include. Although we do not retain, in any easily-retrievable way, the addresses that you are emailing, these emails are not private communications. Also, you may not use these tools to send spam or content that violates the User Agreement.

**Leads/Advisors/Top Reviewers.** While you are a Category Lead, Advisor or Top Reviewer, we may contact you.

**Feedback.** We may ask for your feedback through a survey, and we may use the results for our internal development and marketing research. We may also share the results with our affiliates, consultants, vendors and service providers.   
  
Links to Other Sites   
The Sites contain links to other web sites. Best-price.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. If you have concerns about how other web sites collect and use information about you, make sure to read that site's own privacy policy.   
Changing or Deleting Information About You   
Registered members may update or edit personal information or delete their membership account by accessing their Member Profile or Account information. We try to implement changes to our databases as quickly as possible. However, not all databases may be updated immediately, and some old data may remain in our archives and records. Also, we may be unable to send changes you make to partners, vendors or third party service providers who have already received your data or content. If your account or membership is being terminated or suspended, we may maintain some data to prevent re-registration. We will retain in our files information you have requested to delete in some circumstances, such as to REsolve disputes, analyze programs and enforce our User Agreement. Furthermore, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored "back up" systems.   
Choice/Opt-Out of Best-price.com Email Communications   
At any time (and except for administrative emails discussed above), you have the ability to opt-out of receiving communications from Best-price.com and our partners. To unsubscribe from the Best-price.com email newsletter, contact Customer Support and let us know that you would like to discontinue this service. In addition, each of our email messages contains a link at the bottom of the email for purposes of adjusting your email subscription preferences or to be removed from our mailing list.   
Security   
Best-price.com uses physical, electronic and administrative safeguards, including advanced firewall and password protection for our databases, designed to protect the security of data. We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees that need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.   
Notification of Changes   
This Privacy Policy may be revised over time as our business grows and evolves. We will post any new privacy policy, along with the date of its last revision, prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check the Sites regularly for information about revisions to our privacy policy. If you would like to receive email notification of any such changes, please contact Customer Support requesting the same.   
Anti-Spam Policy   
Best-price.com is 100% opposed to unsolicited commercial email or spam. We do not send emails to anyone without permission and we do not sell or provide email addresses to any unauthorized third party. If you receive any unsolicited emails from spammers, please be assured that Best-price.com did not provide your email addresses to such parties. This does not mean that we can prevent spam from happening on the Internet. If you believe that you have received an unsolicited email from us, please contact our Privacy Department and we will investigate.   
Your Trademark Item   
Should you notice the usage of a trademark term within our search engine campaigns please contact us briefly via email: [campaigns@best-price.com](mailto:campaigns@best-price.com)   
We will immediately cease inadvertent bidding.   
Contact Us   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Sites or Best-price.com, you may contact:  
Best-Price.com Ltd.  
Barfussgaesschen 11  
04109 Leipzig  
Germany  
or our Privacy Department
